https://terryjacobs.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyKathryn David
Last updated: January 17, 2017
Le Tropique, Inc.™ operates https://terryjacobs.com.
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal
Information we receive from users of the Site.
By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that can be
used to contact or identify you. Personal information may include, but is not limited to your name,
address, phone, and email.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site
(“Log Data”).
This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address,
browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit,
the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and
analyze this data to assist in developing strategies intended to improve our site rankings on the
search engines.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional
materials and other information that inform you of new product offerings, coupons, and events.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to
use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security. This site employs SSL security and does not store credit card information on its
domain name servers. Elavon is the merchant gateway to our merchant services provider which
processes all credit cards on our behalf.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 17, 2017, and will remain in effect except with
respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being
posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this
Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the
Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your
consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email
address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Les
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email tropih2o@aol.com
Join Cosmetics For The Tropics Mailing List!
Join my email list to receive updates & exclusive offers!
Sign up & Save!
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Select a country / region…
United States (US)
Select an option…
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces (AA)Armed Forces (AE)Armed Forces (AP)
Update
Go to Top
